

- +639950146553
- christianjoshua0414@gmail.com
- Lives in Malabon city

ABOUT ME

My journey in web development began with a curiosity-driven exploration of HTML, CSS and JavaScript, which ignited my passion for coding. Since then, I have continuously honed my skills and expanded my expertise, staying abreast of the latest industry trends and technologies.

EDUCATION

Information and Communication
Technology - Computer Programming

Access Computer College 2017-2019

Bachelor of Secondary Education Major in English

Lady of Lourdes Caybiga College 2019-2022

LANGUAGE

English

CHRISTIAN JOSHUA PAREÑO

Web Developer

SKILLS

Technical Education and Skills Development Authority (TESDA) Certification:

 Course Title: Computer Systems Servicing

Training Duration: 280 hoursCompletion Date: July 2023

Technical Education and Skills
Development Authority (TESDA)
Certification:

Course Title: Java ProgrammingTraining Duration: 240 hours

• Completion Date: January 2024

EXPERIENCE

Customer Service Representative

Inspiro Irelia Inc. / Retail Account

2022-2023

- In my role as a Retail Account Call Center Representative, I demonstrated a passion for delivering exceptional customer service and driving sales.
- I focus on building strong relationships with customers, expert product knowledge, and a resultsoriented mindset, I made significant contributions to the success of the retail account.

Computer Attendant

Hyper Blitz Gaming Corner

2019-2021

 I utilize my proficiency in diagnosing and resolving technical issues, I ensure that computer systems are functioning optimally at all times. Whether it's troubleshooting hardware malfunctions, resolving software conflicts, or addressing connectivity issues, I am proactive in identifying and resolving problems efficiently.